brackify.com 2018-11-03

# Privacy Policy - Brackify

This Privacy Policy was last updated on December 30, 2016.

 **Our Policy:**

Welcome to Brackify! Brackify LLC., doing business as Brackify ("Brackify," "we," "us" and/or "our"), operates the website located at www.brackify.com and related mobile applications and services (collectively, the "Service"). The Service is designed to serve as a single sign on destination for free-to-create interactive voting brackets and viewing and voting on bracket contests. Through the Service, you may access, view and vote on various voting bracket contests. This Privacy Policy describes how Brackify collects, uses and discloses information, including personally identifiable data ("Personal Data") and other information, that is collected from visitors to the Service.

Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using or submitting information through the Service. By using or submitting information through the service, you are indicating that you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into the Brackify Terms of Service.

 **Information We Collect:**

When you interact with us through the Service, we may collect Personal Data and other information from you, as further described below:

 **Personal Data That You Provide Through the Service:** We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide such information to us, such as when you contact us with inquiries; respond to one of our surveys; register for an account with or access to the Service; participate in promotions, sweepstakes or contests; or use certain features of the Service in connection with gameplay. For instance, when a user registers for an account with the Service, the user is asked to provide an email address. Additional information may be provided to Brackify when users voluntarily connect to the Service through a social media account. Wherever Brackify collects Personal Data, we make an effort to provide a link to this Privacy Policy.

 **User Content:** We may collect and store information that you and other users upload, post, publish or display through the Service, including without limitation user profile pictures and any comments or messages you post to or send through the Service ("User Content"). You acknowledge and agree that, to the extent that you include Personal Data in User Content, such Personal Data will be public, and we are not responsible for how others may use it. Please use caution and common sense when sharing or posting User Content.

You may request that we remove User Content you have previously posted from publicly viewable areas of the Service by contacting us at contact@brackify.com. You understand that such content may remain on publicly viewable areas of the Service if other users have posted or reposted it, and that your User Content may remain on our servers or in our records after it is no longer viewable by other users of the Service.

 **Data You Provide about Others:** We may also collect and store information about others that you provide to us through your use of the Service, such as when you share User Content with others through email or social media websites and services. For more information on the data we share with and receive from social media websites and services, see the section titled "Social Networking Services" below.

By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You represent that the Personal Data you provide is true, accurate, current and complete, and that you have the authorization to provide it to us. If you provide Personal Data to the Service, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of Brackify and the authorized third parties referred to herein located in the United States.

 **IP Addresses; Device ID Information:** The requests you make to Brackify may contain your IP address (the Internet address of your computer). We may use visitors' IP addresses for various purposes, including to display customized content and analyze and report upon the usage of the Service and content, features and services made available through the Service; to diagnose and prevent service or technology problems affecting the Service; and to monitor and prevent fraud and abuse. If you access the Service on a mobile device, we may also collect your device identification number and request access to settings and location information for similar purposes and to personalize your experience with the Service.

 **Location Information:** The Service may collect and use your location information (for example, by using the GPS on your mobile device or through connected Social Networking Services) to provide certain functionality. We may also use your location information in an aggregate way, as described below in the "Aggregated Personal Data" section. The collection and tracking of your location information may occur even when the Service, including any mobile application, is not actively open and running.

You may change the privacy settings of your mobile device to turn off the functionality to share location information with the Service. Please note that turning off location sharing may affect certain features of the Service. If you have any questions about the privacy settings of your mobile device, we recommend that you contact the manufacturer or your mobile service provider for assistance.

 **Other Information:**

 **Non-Identifiable Data:** When you interact with Brackify through the Service, we and third parties that may provide certain functionality on the Service, such as advertising networks, use various technologies to passively collect information that cannot by itself be used to specifically identify you ("non-identifiable data"). Brackify may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by Brackify affiliates, agents or service providers. We may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to the Service, the number of visitors to each page of the Service, the number of visitors and in-game activity per level of gameplay for our games, the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers, and the devices, operating systems and browsers used by our visitors. It is important to note that no Personal Data is available or used in this process.

In operating and providing the Service, we use technologies called "cookies" and "deep links." A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts the Service gives to your browser when you access the Service. Cookies and deep links help us provide additional functionality to the Service, personalize your experience with the Service and analyze Service usage more accurately. For instance, we may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the Service without needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the Service. In all cases in which we use cookies, we will not collect Personal Data except with your permission. On most web browsers, you will find a "help" section on the toolbar. Please refer to this section for information on how to receive notification when you are receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of the Service's features.

We also may use Google Analytics and similar tools to help analyze how users use the Service. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect standard Internet log-in information and visitor behavior information. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Service (including IP address) is transmitted to and stored by Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors' uses of the Service, compile statistical reports on activity on the Service and enhance your experience when you use the Service. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. For more information on how Google uses this data, go to www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/.

 **Response to "Do Not Track" Signals:** At present, we do not respond to "do not track" signals sent from web browsers. If we do so in the future, we will provide all relevant information in this policy.

This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies, deep links and similar technologies by Brackify only. Uses of these or similar technologies by any third-party advertiser or web service linked from the Service (including services of Brackify' Partners and other business partners) are governed by each such advertiser or web service's privacy policy.

When Brackify offers the Service in connection with Partners, such Partners may use other technologies to collect information about you and your use of the Service. The manner in which Partners use, store and disclose your information is governed by the policies of the applicable Partner, and, as a result, Brackify shall not have any liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of a Partner that may be enabled within and/or otherwise accessible through the Service. If you use the Service as offered in connection with a Partner, please review such Partner's privacy policy for a description of how the Partner collects and uses your information.

 **Aggregated Personal Data:** In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Service, Brackify often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and Brackify may share this aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners or otherwise use it for any lawful purpose. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. Brackify may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe the Service to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

 **Our Use of Your Personal Data and Other Information:**

Brackify uses the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, when we offer a game or other Service feature, such as a contest, with a Partner and you register for the game or feature, your Personal Data may be shared with such Partner to facilitate your participation. If you contact us by email, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to the Service, we will use your Personal Data to provide you with access to the Service, to provide you with game notifications and to monitor your use of the Service. Brackify and its subsidiaries and affiliates (the "Brackify Related Companies") may also use your Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the Service to help us improve the content and functionality of the Service, to better understand our users and to improve the Service.

Brackify and its affiliates and Partners may use your Personal Data and other information to communicate with you about content, features, promotions and services we believe will be of interest to you, such as upcoming Brackify or Partner games. We will send such messages only with your consent, which we will ask you for when you register for your account with the Service. If we do so, each communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to "opt-out" of receiving future communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below.

If Brackify intends on using any Personal Data in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Data is collected.

 **Our Disclosure of Your Personal Data and Other Information:**

Brackify considers your information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below (and as previously set forth above):

 **Partners:** We often work with Partners to make available social games, provide content or services, sponsor contests or sweepstakes and display advertisements. If you link to the Service through a Partner's website or service, we may provide such Partner with information about you and your use of the Service, including your Personal Data, the games you play through the Service and your activities during gameplay. We may also share information about your use of the Service with our other Partners on an aggregate basis.

 **Business Transfers:** As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets. We cannot control how an acquiring or surviving entity may use or disclose such information.

 **Related Companies:** We may also share your Personal Data with our Related Companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

 **Agents, Consultants, Vendors and Service Providers:** Brackify, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases and performing customer service. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we only provide such company with the information needed to perform its specific function. Brackify will take measures to ensure that such companies do not use your information for any other purposes.

 **As Required By Law and Similar Disclosures:** Brackify may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Brackify, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability.

 **Your Choices:**

You can use certain features of the Service without providing any Personal Data. If you choose not to provide any Personal Data, you may not be able to use all features of the Service.

 **Exclusions:**

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by Brackify other than Personal Data collected through the Service. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Brackify through the Service or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Service, such as comment sections or bulletin boards (collectively, "Public Areas"), any ideas for new products or services or modifications to existing products or services, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, "Unsolicited Information"). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Brackify shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.

 **Children:**

Brackify does not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Data through the Service. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Data on the Service without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data to Brackify through the Service, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

 **Links to Other Websites:**

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Service. The Service may contain links to other websites not operated or controlled by Brackify (the "Third-Party Sites"). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third-Party Sites. The links from the Service do not imply that Brackify endorses or has reviewed the Third-Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

 **Social Networking Services:**

Through the Service, we may offer you the opportunity to access certain social media and social networking websites and services that are owned and/or controlled by third parties (including, without limitation, Facebook and Twitter) (such websites and services, collectively, the "Social Networking Services"). When you elect to access and use the Social Networking Services, you will be sharing your information (which will include Personal Data if you elect to share such information) with those Social Networking Services. As with other Third-Party Sites, the information that you share with the Social Networking Services will be governed by the privacy policies and terms of service of the providers of such Social Networking Services and not by the policies and procedures we describe here. You may also be able to modify your privacy settings with these Social Networking Services to, for example, control what information the Social Networking Services disclose to other entities, including Brackify. When you log into the Service using a Social Networking account or otherwise link your Brackify account with a Social Networking Service account, we will collect relevant information necessary to enable the Service to access that Social Networking Service; however, you will provide any login information, like your password, directly to such Social Networking Service (and not to Brackify). As part of such integration, the Social Networking Service will provide Brackify with access to certain information that you have provided to such Social Networking Service and information about your use of such Social Networking Service, and we will use, store and disclose such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and, if and to the extent applicable, the policies of such Social Networking Services. However, please remember that the manner in which Social Networking Services use, store and disclose your information is governed by the policies of the applicable Social Networking Services provider, and, as a result, Brackify shall not have any liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of Social Networking Services that may be enabled within and/or otherwise accessible through the Service.

 **Security:**

Brackify takes reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided via the Service from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet or email transmission is ever fully secure or error-free. In particular, email sent to or from the Service may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal Data to Brackify via the Internet.

By using the Service or providing Personal Data to us, you agree that we may communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of the Service. If we learn of a security system's breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically by posting a notice on the Service or by sending an email to you. You may have a legal right to receive this notice in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice), please notify us at contact@brackify.com.

 **International Users:**

All Personal Data is stored on servers in the United States and is subject to United States law. By choosing to use the Service or otherwise provide information to us, you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy will be governed by the law of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts and the adjudication of any disputes arising in connection with Brackify or the Service be in accordance with the Terms of Service.

If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use, please note that you are agreeing to the transfer of your information to the United States and the global processing of such information. By providing your information you consent to any transfer and processing in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

 **Other Terms and Conditions:**

Your access to and use of the Service is subject to the Terms of Service.

 **Changes to Brackify' Privacy Policy:**

The Service and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for Brackify to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Brackify reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Service after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

 **New Uses of Personal Data:** From time to time, we may desire to use Personal Data for uses not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy. If our practices change regarding previously collected Personal Data in a way that would be materially less restrictive than stated in the version of this Privacy Policy in effect at the time we collected the information, we will make reasonable efforts to provide notice and obtain consent to any such uses as may be required by law.

 **Access to Information; Contacting Brackify:**

To keep your Personal Data accurate, current, and complete, you may log in to your account and review and update your information or contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct Personal Data in our possession that you have previously submitted via the Service.

Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about Brackify' Privacy Policy or the information practices of the Service.

You may contact us as follows: contact@brackify.com.

 **** Your California Privacy Rights:**

Applicable California privacy legislation permits visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request to access such information, please contact us at contact@brackify.com. Within thirty (30) days of receiving such a request, we will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified in this paragraph.
